anjolee.com 2013-12-19

# Anjolee.com Privacy Policy – Committed to Protect Your Privacy Online

|  | 

**Collection and Use of Information:**

In general, users can browse our website without revealing their identity or any personal identifiable information.  
Personal identifiable information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including,  
but not limited to, a first and last name; home, billing or other physical address; an email address; phone number  
or other contact information; and a credit card number and expiration date. When you submit your personal  
identifiable information to us, you are giving us your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personally  
identifiable information as set forth in this privacy policy.

The security and protection of our customers' personal information is our top priority. To process your order,  
we require your name, phone number, billing and shipping address, e-mail address, and credit card information.  
We share only necessary information with the third parties that are involved in the order process, such as the  
financial institution that issued your credit card, the shipping carrier, and Anjolee customer service representatives.  
(Note: We would be obligated to disclose individual personal information if Anjolee were to be subpoenaed or  
ordered by a court of law.)

As a policy, Anjolee does not, sell, trade or rent your personally identifiable information to third-parties, unless you  
have granted us permission to do so. We will not share personal information aside from the previously mentioned  
third parties involved in the processing of your order.

 **External Links:** External Links on our site may include links to other sites. If you decide to follow these links,  
we are not responsible for the privacy policies and content of these sites. Generally, we will inform you of these links.

 **Communications:** If you provide Anjolee with personally identifiable information, this information may be used  
to communicate to you information regarding Anjolee and its products and services. For example, we may  
communicate to you information regarding promotions, surveys, contests, sweepstakes or product or  
service updates. Your personally identifiable information may also be used to improve and customize our  
Web Site's content, layout and services. These uses improve and customize our interactions with you  
to better meet your needs.

 **Compliance with Law and Fraud Protection:** We may collect and disclose any information, including personally  
identifiable information, we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation,  
legal process or governmental request. We may collect and possibly share personally identifiable information  
and any other information available to us in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities,  
suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any personal or as otherwise  
required by law. We may also exchange information, including personally identifiable information, with other  
companies and organizations for credit fraud protection and risk reduction.

 **Choice Opt Out:** We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. To opt-out of receiving  
communications from Anjolee: (1) select "unsubscribe" on our subscription status page and enter the  
requested information; or (2) make your request in person by contacting a diamond and jewelry consultant  
at 877-ANJOLEE (265-6533) or by e-mail at [service@anjolee.com](mailto:service@anjolee.com).

 **Your Consent to Anjolee Privacy Policy**

By using this Web Site, you agree to Anjolee's privacy policy. This is our entire and exclusive privacy policy and  
it supersedes any earlier version. We may occasionally update this privacy policy. When a revision is made we  
will revise the "last updated" date on this page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy policy to stay  
informed about how we are protecting your information. Your continued use of this Web Site constitutes your  
consent to this privacy policy and any updates.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use  
information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this  
and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would  
like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used  
by these companies, [click here](http://www.fetchback.com/optout.html).

If you have questions or concerns about our policy, you may contact Anjolee customer service  
at [service@anjolee.com](mailto:service@anjolee.com) or 877-ANJOLEE (265-6533).  
  
---|---
